Day 1,000
of the siege of Seattle.
The Muslim community demands an end
to the Army's occupation of mosques.
The Homeland Security bill
is ratified.
After eight years,
British borders will remain closed.
The deportation of illegal immigrants
will continue.
Good morning. Our lead story.
The world was stunned
today by the death of Diego Ricardo,
the youngest person on the planet.
Baby Diego was stabbed
outside a bar in Buenos Aires
after refusing to sign an autograph.
- Witnesses at the scene say...
- Excuse me.
..that Diego spat in the face of a fan
who asked for an autograph.
He was killed in the ensuing brawl.
- The fan was later beaten to death...
- Coffee, please. Black.
...by the angry crowd.
Born in 2009,
the son of Marcello and Sylvia Ricardo,
a working-class couple from Mendoza,
he struggled all his life
with the celebrity status
thrust upon him
as the world's youngest person.
Diego Ricardo,
the youngest person on the planet,
was 18 years, 4 months...
...20 days, 16 hours, and 8 minutes old.
Throughout his life,
Diego Ricardo was a tragic reminder
of the 18 years of infertility
that humanity has endured
and its effect upon the world
we now live in.
It seems that the mantle of the world's
youngest human has passed to a woman.
She is 18 years, 5 months,
and 11 days old.
Faron.
Mr. Giriffiths.
I seem to be more affected by
Baby Diego's death than I realised, sir.
If you wouldn't mind, I'd appreciate it
if I could finish my day's work at home.
...generation needs
to reject family and society.
He's my dentist.
She's my house cleaner.
- He's the waiter.
- She's my cousin.
They are illegal immigrants.
To hire, feed or shelter
illegal immigrants is a crime.
It's your life.
It's your choice.
Hey, amigo!
Jasper!
Good to see you. Come on.
- You know who did it?
- Islamic? Fishes? Fuck knows.
I'll bet it was the government.
Every time one of our politicians
Is in trouble, a bomb explodes.
It's the second time in a month.
You okay?
It was horrible.
I'm glad you don't take
cream or sugar, amigo.
Losing you and Baby Diego
on the same day would be too hard to bear.
Well, that was even worse,
everybody crying.
I mean, Baby Diego, come on.
That guy was a wanker.
Yeah, but he was
the youngest wanker on Earth.
Pull my finger. Quick, quick!
Jasper...
Fucking hell! That's disgusting!
Illegal immigrants.
Taking them to Bexhill.
Poor fugees.
After escaping the worst atrocities
and finally making it to England,
our government hunts them down
like cockroaches.
Any girls?
No.
What about the one
we had lunch with? Lauren?
Lorna. That was ages ago.
I liked her. What happened?
She decided to renounce.
Renouncers? Are those the ones
that kneel down for a month for salvation?
No. They're the Repenters.
The Renouncers flagellate themselves
for the forgiveness of humanity.
Oh, right.
Dating ain't what it used to be,
Is it, amigo?
- What'd you do on your birthday?
- Nothing.
Come on.
You must've done something.
No. Same as every other day.
Woke up, felt like shit,
went to work, felt like shit.
That's called a hangover,
amigo.
At least with a hangover,
I feel something.
Honestly, Jasper, sometimes...
You could always come and live with us.
Yeah, but if I did that, I wouldn't
have anything to look forward to.
Look who it is. It's Theo.
- Hey, Janice, how you doing?
- It's Theo.
Your rebel with a lost cause.
She loves this color.
Don't you, darling? You love it.
"Is there a chance
it will not work for me?
"There have been no cases
of anyone surviving
"who has taken the preparation.”
Daddy Government
hands out suicide kits,
and anti-depressants in the rations,
but ganja is still illegal.
Most of my weed goes to Bexhill, now.
This bloke buys it from me
and smuggles it in.
Guess what he does? His real job?
Immigration cop.
Bravo!
One of the many perks of having
a refugee camp in the neighbourhood.
Come on, taste that.
Cough.
- Cough?
- Cough.
You taste it? Strawberries.
This is Strawberry Cough.
So, Human Project is having this dinner
and all the wisest men
in the world are there...
"Human Project".
Why do people believe this crap?
You know, even if these people existed
with these facilities in secret locations...
Fuck me, that's strong.
Even if they discovered the cure
for infertility, it doesn't matter.
Too late. The world went to shit.
You know what?
It was too late before the infertility thing
happened, for fuck's sake.
I was just trying to tell a joke, man.
I'm sorry. Go on.
- No, I'm not telling it now.
- No, come on, Jasper.
- No. Fuck it. I'm not fucking telling you.
- It's all right. Go on.
Okay. The Human Project
gives this great big dinner
for all the scientists
and sages in the world.
They're tossing around theories
about the ultimate mystery,
why are women infertile?
Why can't we make babies anymore?
Some of them say
it's genetic experiments,
gamma rays, pollution.
Same old, same old.
Anyway, in the corner,
this Englishman's sitting.
He hasn't said a word.
He's just tucking into his dinner.
So they decide to ask him.
They say, "Well, why do you think
we can't make babies anymore?"
And he looks up at them,
and he's chewing on this great big wing,
and he says, "I haven't
the faintest idea," he said.
"But this stork is quite tasty, isn't it?"
Eating a fucking stork.
Eating the stork.
Italia.
You okay, amigo?
Yeah. My ears are still ringing
from earlier.
Well, a little Zen music
won't bother you, then, will it?
Good morning.
The time is 7:59 a.m.
British citizens,
hold out your I.D. cards.
All others, follow instructions.
What the fuck?
Move along! Move along!
This is him.
- Get your fucking head down!
- Walk!
Get your fucking head down!
- Okay. Okay.
- Get in!
- Get him in! Get him in!
- Get his fucking legs.
Go, go, go, go!
You are under
the jurisdiction of the Fishes.
The Fishes are at war
with the British government
until they recognise equal rights
for every immigrant in Britain.
We're not gonna hurt you.
We just want to talk.
But don't do anything stupid.
- Uncover him.
- It isn't safe.
Do it.
Hello, Theo.
It's me, Theo. It's Julian.
You scared the shit out of me.
I'm sorry about the theatrics,
but we had no choice.
The police have been
a pain in the ass lately.
How have you been?
Fantastic. Couldn't be better.
Cut the lights.
The police keep using
that old photo of you in the posters.
It doesn't do you justice.
What do the police know
about justice?
What exactly is it you guys do,
anyway?
The Fishes fight for equal rights
for every immigrant in Britain!
He knows what we do.
I know you almost blew me up
in a coffee shop yesterday.
My ears are still ringing.
- We don't bomb.
- That was the government.
- That's what they do to spread the fear.
- What about Liverpool?
After Liverpool,
we stopped bombing.
We started speaking to the people.
And they're joining us, Theo.
British people, too.
- I don't talk politics.
- That's all you ever used to do.
That was 20 years ago.
I'm a lot more successful now.
Come on, Theo. Walk with me.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- Come on!
You're smoking?
Yeah. It's not working.
I heard about your mother. I'm sorry.
Were your parents in New York
when it happened?
- Yeah.
- Shit.
Yeah, well, that's the world
we live in now, isn't it?
Why am I here, Jules?
I need your help.
I need transit papers.
Not for me. A girl, she's a fugee.
Need to get her to the coast,
past security checkpoints.
I haven't seen you for nearly 20 years
and you come asking me for transit papers?
Can you do it?
I don't see how.
You could ask your cousin.
The government finances his Ark of the Arts.
He has access to papers.
Yeah, but he'd never do it.
He would if you asked him.
I can't. It's too dangerous.
I can get you £5,000.
I know you need the money.
What are you talking about?
I don't fucking need your money.
Right. Sorry.
My mistake.
You know that ringing
in your ears? That...
That's the sound of the ear cells dying.
Like their swan song.
Once it's gone,
you'll never hear that frequency again.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
This never fucking happened,
so don't go telling tales,
'cause we'll be watching you.
At work, when you sleep,
when you have a piss, we'll be watching.
All the fucking time.
Jeez, your breath stinks.
- No, it doesn't.
- Yes, it does.
It was Julian's idea
bringing you here.
She put herself at great risk.
Now you know about
the five grand we can offer you.
So, if you change your mind,
pin this to the notice board
at Camden tube. We'll do the rest.
Here you are. Bus fare.
Earthquakes! Pollution!
Disease and famine!
Our sins have encouraged God's wrath!
And in his anger he has taken away
his most precious gift to us!
Mr. Faron, the minister is
expecting you. This way, sir.
I'm afraid this is a non-smoking facility.
You got something in your teeth.
If you'll excuse me.
Couldn't save La Pieta.
Smashed up before we got there.
Pretty rummy, huh?
My mum had a plastic one
in the bathroom.
It was a lamp.
Good to see you, Theo.
We got to keep Las Meninas
and a few other Velásquezes,
but we only got a hold of two Goyas.
That thing in Madrid
was a real blow to art.
Not to mention people.
How's Martha?
She's doing her animal
charity thing. Sends her love.
- Give her my best.
- Yes.
Why did you come, Theo?
Well, the thing is,
I met this girl.
Cute?
Beautiful.
Is it serious?
Very.
She's got this brother in Brighton and
she hasn't seen him for about five years,
and he's not doing too good.
I mean, pretty sick.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
Sorry.
I've got money.
I was just hoping that you might...
I was hoping you could get us
the transit papers to get to the coast.
Transit papers?
That's quite a favour.
I know.
Highly controlled.
Alex, take your pills.
Alex.
Alex?
Alex!
Come with me.
I'm really sorry, Nigel.
I just don't know who else to ask.
I'll see what I can do.
What?
You kill me.
A hundred years from now,
there won't be one sad fuck
to look at any of this.
What keeps you going?
You know what it is, Theo?
I just don't think about it.
Where's Julian?
She couldn't make it.
Sends her best.
Here's a photo of the girl and her name.
Hang on. We got a problem.
All I could get were joint transit papers,
which means
I would have to escort the girl.
Will you?
For a couple more grand.
Julian thinks very highly of you.
Does she?
Yeah.
Thanks again.
Go on, stay with her.
Stay with her.
Stay with her. Yes!
Have you seen this dog?
I'll be one minute.
Billy! I'm in a rush, mate.
Okay, Theo.
He'll see to you. He'll see to you.
I'm in a rush. Come on. Come on.
That's 70 quid.
Shit.
She's my house cleaner.
He's the plumber.
Jesus.
He's my dentist.
He's the waiter.
She's my cousin.
They are illegal immigrants.
To hire, feed or shelter
illegal immigrants is a crime.
Protect Britain.
Report all illegal immigrants.
Did you get the papers?
Lovely to see you, too.
Thank you.
I really appreciate this.
Just like the old days,
back of the bus.
Yeah, except we're the old farts now.
- You're looking good.
- Right.
Seriously. Look at me.
It's hard for me to look at you.
He had your eyes.
You know, I never understood
how you got over it so quickly.
You think I got over it?
No one could get over it.
I live with it. I think about him every day.
Come on, I mean the way you just...
You don't have a monopoly
on suffering, you know.
You always carried his memory
like a ball and chain...
What do you fucking know
about my memories?
- You don't know what I feel or what...
- Move!
Yeah, there you go.
That's what you always do.
When it gets tough, you walk away.
This is our stop.
Thelonius!
Andiamo!
So why did you come to me?
You could have found
other ways to get transit papers.
Probably.
So why me?
I trust you.
And what happens after?
You take a train back. It'll be safer.
No, I mean what happens to us?
I don't know.
Theo, come on.
You came for the money.
Did I?
Theo?
- You got my money?
- See?
We'll take you down to the first
checkpoint on the Canterbury Road,
then you and Kee are on your own.
Well, this is obviously the elite unit.
- This is Miriam.
- Hi.
Is this the girl?
Kee, this is Theo.
What the fuck you staring at?
Apparently the pleasure's all mine.
Are we planning a sing-along?
Good. I'm gonna take a nap.
The afternoon is looking
good here on Radio Avalon.
And now one for all
the nostalgics out there,
a blast from the past
all the way back from 2003.
That beautiful time
when people refused to accept
the future was just around the corner.
Hey.
You're snoring.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you were. He always snored.
Where are we?
Canterbury. We're close.
Anyone know
if there's a hotel around here?
What?
Julian promised me
a little bit of action.
You still like it in the afternoon?
So what did you do?
Rob a train? Blow up a building?
Leave the girl alone.
You told me he was suave.
Wanker's a drunk.
He's suave. You should have seen him
in the old days when he was a real activist.
You were the activist,
I just wanted to get laid.
One time the police came
to throw us out of our squat
and Theo invited them up
for coffee to negotiate,
only the coffee
was spiked with ketamine.
No! You didn't, did you?
Fuck off. You gotta be kidding.
You know how many people
I've tried this with?
I don't wanna know.
You'll be happy to know
out of the hundreds...
- Hundreds?
- ...you are still the only one.
- I'm not doing it.
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not. The car's moving too much.
- Yes, you are. Yes, you are.
You are. Ready?
Thelonius!
No, wait, wait. Okay.
Do it again!
Julian, that's disgusting!
Look out!
Jesus! Shit!
Go! Go! We're gonna make it.
Come on, we're gonna make it.
No, I'm not gonna make it!
I'm not gonna make it!
- Christ!
- Back up! Back up now!
Jesus!
Oh, save us! Save us
in our hour of need!
Blessed Mary, save us.
Christ, Jesus!
- He's got a gun!
- Cover Keel!
Get down!
- Shit!
- Oh, my God!
She's been shot!
Fuck. She's been shot.
How is she? How is she?
She's bleeding!
She's bleeding,
she's bleeding everywhere!
- Shit!
- Julian.
Put pressure on the wound!
Please, please, please.
Please, please.
Oh, no.
Julian...
Jesus Christ!
Julian!
It's the cops. It's the cops.
Did they see us?
Keep going. Speed up.
- Are they coming back?
- Faster! Faster!
What's happening?
- Are they coming back?
- I don't know. Just go faster!
Can't you pull off the road?
All right, slow down. Slow down!
I can't outrun them.
- Stop the car.
- I gotta stop. I gotta stop.
Pull over 10 the side of the road.
Stop the car!
Get your passports out!
Stay inside the vehicle!
We're British citizens!
- British citizens!
- Hands on the steering wheel!
Hands on the steering wheel!
Calm down. Tell me what's happened!
We were attacked!
We gotta take her to a hospital.
Okay. Just wait.
I'm gonna call for assistance.
What are you doing?
- Get in the car.
- Why did you do that?
Get in the fucking car!
Get back in now. Quickly.
We gotta get off the road. Get in. Get in.
Go! Go! Go!
We have to call on help now.
Put your hands out.
Fucking shit.
May all the ascended beings,
the bodhisattvas and saints
and all those who have walked the surface
of the earth in the light of eternal truth,
come to the aid
of our beloved sister, Julian.
Theo! Come on!
Theo, come on!
This is Tomasz and Emily's farm.
I already called
and told them the situation.
We'll be safe here.
Fishes are coming in
to vote for a new leader.
- Ian?
- Yeah.
- We have to convene.
- Everyone's arriving.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, it's not my blood.
- Emily, Tomasz, this is Kee.
- Welcome.
Miriam.
They need to wash up and rest.
How about Julian's mate?
Yeah, can somebody give me
a lift back to London?
No, no, no.
It's too dangerous. We'll sort it tomorrow.
Tomasz, get him a shower
and a clean shirt.
Tomasz, don't block the car in.
It needs to be jump-started. Ian?
Yeah.
They like you.
And they don't like anyone.
You did what you could.
We need to show
strength and unity.
The shirt fit?
Yeah, it's fine. Thanks.
I'll take care of this.
As head Fishes,
we need to make a choice now.
We need to choose leadership.
I don't think
that those bloodstains will wash off.
Don't worry about it.
Throw it away.
I'm in charge of watching you.
Why?
They told me.
Well, I'm going back
to London tomorrow.
I lived there once. Didn't like it.
No.
They kill you.
Where you from?
Poland.
Is this your place?
My missus. She's a cod.
English Fish.
Mr. Faron.
Kee would like a word with you.
She's in the barn. It's all right, Tomasz.
I'll watch him.
Hey, don't smoke in the barn.
To Luke,
our new leader. Luke.
- To Luke.
- Luke.
Viva Ia Luke!
I'll be right outside.
You know what they do
to these cows?
They cut off their tits. They do.
Gone. Bye.
Only leave four.
Four tits fits the machine.
It's wacko. Why not make machines
that suck eight titties?
Is that what you want to talk about?
Cows and titties?
Julian told me about your baby.
Said his name was Dylan.
You taught him to swim when he was two.
He called you "Papa.”
She said if anything goes spooky,
I should talk to you.
Said you'd help me,
said you'd get me to the boat.
- What boat?
- The Tomorrow.
The Tomorrow?
I don't know what you're talking about.
But I'm sure your friends
can take care of you.
But Julian said only trust you.
She said you'd help me.
I don't know why she said that.
Listen, I don't quite know
what's going on.
You can't leave.
Kee, I'm in a lot of trouble myself.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait!
What are you doing? Don't do that.
I'm scared.
Please help me.
Jesus Christ.
- Kee! Keel!
- What are you doing?
Are you all right?
She wanted him to know.
She has the right.
Of course, she has.
For God's sake.
When you're ready, come inside.
Everybody's arrived.
She's pregnant.
Now you know what's at stake.
But she's pregnant.
Yeah, I know.
It's a miracle, isn't it?
Fishes terrorist leader
Julian Taylor was killed today
in a gun battle with police
near Canterbury.
Four other terrorists escaped
after murdering two officers.
Police say they have sufficient
forensic and surveillance evidence
to identify the four killers.
All suspects should be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
This was broadcast an hour ago.
We have to assume
it's just a matter of time
before they identify the rest of us,
which includes you, Theo.
- Why is he here?
- He's not a Fish.
He's not one of us.
I want him here.
Kee wants him, he stays.
Now, we all agreed to deliver Kee to our
brothers and sisters in the Human Project.
Right.
Now we got to re-evaluate that position.
No, there's no need.
We move forward with the original plan.
Yes!
She'll never make it.
The police are looking for her.
We can find a way.
It's what Julian wanted.
We'd be risking the girl's life.
Listen, listen! She belongs here.
And this baby is the flag
that could unite us all!
We said we'd never use
this baby for political purposes.
My baby's not a flag.
Make it public!
What?
- What?
Excuse me?
You should make it public.
You saw the telly.
She's about to be very public.
It doesn't matter. She's pregnant.
Oh, right. And then
the government will say,
"We were wrong.
Fugees are humans, too."
Well, whatever is going on,
whatever your political ideas are,
it's irrelevant.
- It doesn't matter.
- Aw, come on...
- She needs a doctor.
- You really don't get it.
Look, the government
will take her baby
and parade a posh black
English lady as the mother.
- And she'll never see it again.
- Nobody's taking my baby!
We all know this government
would never acknowledge
the first human birth
in 18 years from a fugee.
A wanted fugee.
Why don't we explain to Mr Faron
what they do to immigrants in this country?
He knows.
He's seen the cages. He's not that stupid.
I'm not going to the government.
You told me you would
get me to the Human Project.
- You promised me.
- I know.
And we will.
But I don't think it's safe to
try and reach the coast now.
You could stay here, Kee. It's a safe place
for you to have your child.
And when you and the baby
are well enough,
we will find a way to get you
to the Human Project.
I promise you, Kee.
It could take months
to get back in touch with them again.
This is true.
We have to take it under consideration.
Kee, this is your decision.
What do you think?
I think you need proper care.
Oh, brilliant!
She has proper care!
- What the fuck does he know?
- Hang on. Kee?
Kee, this is your choice.
- I have my baby here...
- Yes!
...then you get me
to the Human Project.
Thank you, Kee. Thank you.
We need to organise
safe houses.
No more than three days
in one place.
No, no, you can't
keep moving her around.
- It's for her safety.
- Ow!
Please help him!
What are you doing?
- He's hurt really badly!
- Oh, shit, fuck.
I didn't have
anywhere else to go.
You're not supposed to be here!
There's fucking police everywhere!
- What do you think you're doing?
- He's been bleeding for hours!
Shut up! Get his bike
out of here. Get it out!
It's a simple fucking plan.
Get in here, Patric!
What the fuck are you doing here?
No fucking excuses!
You have a first aid kit? Medicine?
Mostly for cows.
Iodine, bandages, clean towels,
whatever you have, bring it to the barn.
And for God's sake,
hide the fucking motorcycle.
You put everything at risk.
What was I supposed to do?
What about all the fucking police, Ian?
You said it would be safe!
We paid the gang.
We had no idea about the cops.
You broke the protocol.
What were you thinking?
What was I thinking?
You could be responsible
for putting the Uprising in jeopardy.
He needs a proper doctor!
Don't you get it?
We have a baby.
When people see we have a baby,
everyone will join us in the Uprising.
But we can forget about the baby
if the girl even suspects we killed Julian!
What was I supposed to do?
You saw how he is.
He's on death's fucking door!
- Take it easy.
- You broke protocol.
He's my fucking cousin!
Luke, he needs a doctor.
Don't worry.
We'll take care of him. Simon, right?
Aye, Simon.
All right, sit down, Patric.
Simon is a good Fish. So are you.
Be proud to know that because of
the two of you, the Uprising is assured.
The baby will stay with us.
Where's Faron?
He's a fucking dead man.
No. Tomorrow.
We'll do him then, after we move the girl.
Patric, you ever break protocol again,
I'll have to kill you.
Kee. Kee, it's Theo.
- Listen to me.
- What's going on?
Luke killed Julian.
They want your baby. They killed Julian.
They're gonna...
They killed Julian. They're gonna kill me.
We have to leave. We have to go now.
Miriam, shut up!
Trust me, we've got to go.
Stop it! Stop it! Both of you!
Get off!
I'm going with him.
Miriam, you can stay if you want.
Miriam, you have to
keep your mouth shut.
- I mean it.
- All right. All right.
We're moving the girl
to Bristol straight away.
We need to bring weapons over...
The refugee camps...
Zaphyr,
he looks bloody fucking awful.
Yeah. Really?
All that dirt and sand in there,
nowhere to hide the blood in, no skin.
Shit! It's fucking disgusting.
He's not gonna make it.
Of course not gonna make it,
with all the blood and guts coming out.
Hey, Samir.
Shit.
Stop! Stop the car!
Stop the fucking car!
Don't shoot!
Don't shoot! The girl's in the car!
- Stop!
- The girl's in the car!
Stop the fucking car!
Give me the fucking keys.
Get down! Get down!
Can't you get it moving any faster?
For God's sake!
Come on. Come on.
Stop!
Shit.
They're coming!
Get going, get going!
They're getting closer!
Oh, God! He's gaining on us!
Can I shoot? I got a clean shot!
Fuck off!
Miriam, jump-start the car!
We have to go!
Wait till it gets faster!
All right! All right!
Just push, you push!
Fucking hell!
Miriam! Miriam!
We have to wait for him! Theo!
Go, go, go!
Kee, are you all right?
I'm fine.
We need to find a safe house.
Yeah, the last one
was really fucking safe.
Well, what do you suggest?
Don't worry. I know where to go.
Wait here.
Oh, fuck.
Ow! Fuck.
Jasper?
Janice?
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck you.
What are you doing with this shit?
This? I mix it with bread
to poison the rats.
It's not bullshit what they say.
They pass away quite peacefully.
Jasper.
Meet Miriam and Kee.
The Tomorrow is a hospital ship
disguised as a fishing boat.
They'll take us to the Human Project.
I told you, amigo,
the Human Project is real.
Yeah, but you're also the guy
that believes in UFOs.
Tell them about that thing
you saw on the heath.
You saw a UFO?
Did you know that the Human Project
Is supposed to have
a community on the Azores?
It's a sanctuary.
That's where they'll take us, Kee.
Can you catch this ship anywhere else?
It's going to stop at the last two
weather buoys en route at sunset.
So it will be tonight at Windsmore
and then two night's time at Bexhill.
You can forget about Windsmore.
We'd never make it in time.
No, it's our only chance.
We can't get to Bexhill.
That's a refugee camp.
Eureka! Eat and rest.
With a little bit of luck,
you're going to need all your energy.
Where are you going?
Feed her for me, Theo.
Kee, your baby is the miracle
the whole world
has been waiting for.
Shanthi, shanthi, shanthi.
Come on. Come on.
Did he really see a UFO?
Is she doing her voodoo hoodoo?
She's doing something.
She smited me with that.
Said it was good for my baby.
Does she look posh to you, or gawky?
Earnest.
Yeah.
How many months?
Eight.
It takes nine months.
I know.
Who's the father?
Whiffet. I'm a virgin.
Sorry?
That'd be wicked, eh?
Yeah, it would.
Fuck knows. I don't know
most of the wankers' names.
You know, when I started puking,
I thought I catch the pest.
But then my belly started getting big.
Nobody ever told me these things.
I never seen a pregnant woman before.
But I knew.
I felt like a freak.
I didn't tell nobody.
I thought about the Quietus thing.
Supposed to be suave.
Pretty music and all that.
Then the baby kicked.
I feel it. Little bastard was alive.
And I feel it. And me, too.
I am alive.
Froley.
Name my baby Froley.
It's the first baby in 18 years.
- You can't call it "Froley".
- Says who?
Kee, I've found you a boat.
- Great.
- How?
We get ourselves arrested.
- Oh, Jesus.
- No, no.
Syd, this border guard I sell pot to,
has agreed to get us into Bexhill.
Nicely ironic, eh?
We break into prison!
Wicked.
"Froley."
Come on.
Everything is
a mythical cosmic battle
between faith and chance.
Maybe I shouldn't.
You already did.
Take another one.
Now cough.
What do you taste?
Strawberries.
Strawberries?
That's what it's called. Strawberry Cough.
Wicked.
So, you've got faith over here, right,
and chance over there.
- Like yin and yang.
- Sort of.
Or Shiva and Shakti.
Lennon and McCartney.
Look, Julian and Theo.
Yeah, there you go.
Julian and Theo met among
a million protesters in a rally
by chance.
But they were there
because of what they believed in
in the first place, their faith.
They wanted to change the world.
And their faith kept them together.
But by chance, Dylan was born.
This is him?
Yeah, that's him. He would have been
about your age. Magical child.
Beautiful.
- Their faith put in praxis.
- Praxis?
What happened?
Chance.
He was their sweet little dream.
He had little hands, little legs, little feet.
Little lungs.
And in 2008,
along came the flu pandemic.
And then, by chance,
he was gone.
Oh, Jesus.
You see, Theo's faith
lost out to chance.
So,
why bother if life's going
to make its own choices?
- Watcha! Baby's got Theo's eyes.
- Yeah.
Oh, boy. That's terrible.
But, you know,
everything happens for a reason.
That I don't know.
But Theo and Julian would
always bring Dylan. He loved it here.
It's the alarm!
Someone's breaking in!
What is it?
Look at this.
Shit.
Jasper, hurry up!
Where's Janice?
Take the back path to the main road,
then follow the map I've given Miriam.
- Yeah, I've got it.
- What are you talking about?
Wait for Syd at the old school
on Watchbell Road in Rye.
Give him this,
and tell him he's a fascist pig.
We need to get Janice.
We're not going, Theo.
What are you talking about?
You don't need an anchor.
No, Jasper. You're coming.
You need time. We'll stall them.
I'll send them the wrong way.
It's the best idea. Go on. Go on.
Jasper.
Theo, I've talked my way out
of worse things than this. Believe me.
Go on. Go.
And remember, tell Syd he's a fascist pig.
I love you.
Hey, amigos!
We're looking for Theo Faron.
We know he was here
a few weeks ago. Has he been back?
- Who?
- Theo Faron.
I haven't seen him in weeks.
There's biscuits and coffee on inside!
Help yourself.
You want a drag?
Come on, have a drag. Lighten up.
- What we got?
- Here, Luke.
There's a dead woman and dog inside.
They're going to Bexhill.
When did they leave?
Pull my finger, go on.
Pull my finger.
I'll do it.
Fuck you.
Pull my finger.
Theo, I'm so sorry.
Don't you fucking touch me.
You tell me the fucking reason in that.
- It's all part of a bigger thing.
- Shut up!
Shut up and get in the fucking car.
Jasper?
He's fine.
Everything's fine.
I was 31.
Midwife at the John Radcliffe.
I was doing a stint in the antenatal clinic.
Three of my patients miscarried
in one week.
Others were
in their fifth and sixth month.
We managed to save
two of the poor babies.
Next week, five more miscarried.
Then the miscarriages
started happening earlier.
I remember booking a woman
in for her next appointment
and noticing that the page
seven months ahead was completely blank.
Not a single name.
I rang a friend
who was working at Queen Charlotte's,
and she had no new pregnancies either.
She then rang her sister in Sydney.
And it was the same thing there.
You can relax. She's finished.
As the sound of the playgrounds faded,
the despair set in.
Very odd what happens
in a world without children's voices.
I was there at the end.
Now you're gonna be
there at the beginning.
Yeah.
I'll be there at the beginning.
Thank you.
Kee, come on! We've got to go!
Stop where you are.
I'm looking for Syd.
Hands above your head.
You're a fascist pig.
What did you say?
I was told to tell you you're a fascist pig.
Say it again.
No, don't, please!
Say it!
You're a fascist pig.
Come on.
It was Jasper's idea, you know.
The whole password thing.
He will piss himself laughing
when I tell him about this.
He's a cheeky old bastard.
So proud of his weed.
Syd could get it a lot
cheaper from the gangs,
but Syd likes to deal with Jasper.
Jasper's straight. A true gentleman.
All right.
What's wrong with her? Is she sick?
Just carsick.
- She's not going to puke, is she?
- No. She's fine.
Puking's bad. Very, very bad.
It doesn't wash out.
The smell never goes away.
Usually, there's people trying
to get out of Bexhill, not in.
Syd doesn't know why you want to get in.
Syd doesn't want to know.
Syd doesn't care.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
What's wrong with her?
A minor contraction.
It's normal. Just breathe.
All right.
When you're released,
stroll out with the other fugees.
Look for the statue of a soldier.
There you'll meet a woman,
Marichka. Arab, gypsy, something.
Always carries a shitty little dog with her.
She'll find you accommodation for tonight.
All right. You're fugees now.
Show Syd the fugee face.
Sad face.
Sad fugee face.
That's good. That's good.
Okay. Out!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Hurry up. Hurry up, move.
Send me a postcard.
Seats in the back!
Come on, hurry up!
What time are we supposed
to meet the boat?
Sunset tomorrow.
How do we know that Luke
and his mob haven't intercepted it?
Luke has no way of contacting
the Human Project. Nor does anyone else.
Say again?
Contact with the Human Project
is done by mirrors.
Julian was our mirror.
What do you mean, "mirrors"?
Mirrors. They contact one of our people.
That person contacts someone else,
and so on, till word gets to Julian.
She tells Luke.
You mean you never actually
talked to any of them?
Uh-uh.
Don't fucking tell me
you never actually talked to them?
All right.
- Breathe it out.
- Is she okay?
That's it. Breathe it out,
breathe it out.
I can't fucking breathe.
You sure this is normal?
It shouldn't be this frequent.
Come on, breathe it out.
All right, all right.
Miriam,
I'm all wet.
Her water's broke. The baby's coming.
Shit. Shit!
All right, sweetheart. All right, sweetheart.
Everything is fine. Breathe.
Just breathe it out. That's it.
Tomorrow you'll be safe.
You'll be on the boat.
On the Tomorrow, they'll take care of you.
They'll take you far away from all this.
Look up, you piece of shite. Look up.
Out!
Get out!
Lord, give Kee the strength to know that
she has the power already within her.
- She has the wisdom...
- What's wrong with you?
I said, what's wrong with you?
Look at me!
Saint Gabriel, help us...
Shut up!
You! Out!
Saint Gabriel, come to our aid!
Listen, you fucking nutcase! Get out!
- Up, now. Come on.
- Caca! Caca!
Piss. Piss. Caca. Smell. Girl.
You smell it yourself.
You fucking people disgust me.
She's okay, Kee. She's okay.
- She's gonna be...
- Miriam!
Move it! Come along now!
Come on, shift it! Shift it! You!
Get down there. Down there. Move.
Follow the line!
- Theo!
- Kee!
- Take it off!
- Theo!
Come on, move!
Move it! Come on!
Move it! Move it!
Come on! Move! Move!
Britain supports you
and provides you shelter.
Do not support terrorists.
Britain supports you
and provides you shelter.
Do not support terrorists.
Hey you, buddy!
Buddy, buddy, welcome to paradise!
You want accommodations?
I got running water! I got...
Just leave the girl alone.
- Who the fuck are you to tell me what to do?
- Fuck off.
- Who do you fucking think you are?
Don't mind these bastards.
I'll take care of you.
Come on, I've got a room, food,
a place to stay. What do you need?
- I'm fine, thanks.
- You must need something, man.
"Fuck off," is it? Bollocks.
Marichka?
It's okay, Kee.
Just breathe through it.
That's it. It's okay.
We're almost there, Kee.
We're almost there.
It's just a few stairs.
Just hold onto me.
I've got you.
Just keep breathing.
Marichka? How far?
How far?
We're almost there, Kee.
Almost there.
You're doing great. Come on.
You're almost there. Three more steps.
We're there, Kee. We're there.
Okay, there's a bed. Easy.
Make her go! Make her go!
That's great. Thank you.
Get her out!
Thank you.
Okay, Kee.
I'm going to put my coat underneath.
You'll be cleaner.
You're okay.
Okay?
There's water.
I'm just going to wash my hands.
Theo! Theo!
I'm here. Fuck!
It's okay. Everything's okay.
Do something!
It's looking good, Kee.
It's looking good.
You're doing great.
Just keep breathing.
- Keep breathing.
- I am breathing!
No, like Miriam said.
Do you remember?
Breathe out.
Just think about the out.
Breathe out and push. Push as well.
- That's it. That's it!
- I can't!
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can. Just out and push.
Out and push.
- That's it!
-I can't do it, Theo. Stop it, please.
Kee, I can see the head.
I can see the head.
You're doing great.
You're doing great, Kee.
That's it. That's it.
It's coming again.
Just breathe out and push. Out and push.
- That's it. Out and...
- I can't.
- You can. Yes, you can.
- I fucking can't!
- Yes, you fucking can! Come on!
- | can't do It
Kee, the head's coming out.
That's it, you're nearly there!
You're nearly there. Just push!
Push, Kee! Push!
Push!
Oh, my God.
How is he?
It's a girl.
Kee, you've got a girl.
Hey, baba.
Aren't we supposed
to cut the cord?
Yeah, it's okay.
There's no rush.
You've done it.
Kee,
see?
It wasn't that bad.
Oh, yeah, not for you.
Come on! Hurry up!
We don't have much time!
Who is it?
The King of England.
Open the door, you asshole. It's Syd.
How can you sleep through
when the whole city's going to hell?
What's wrong with her?
She's fine. It's a woman's thing.
Fuck off!
A few hours ago, a bomb
blew a hole in the fence and fugees got out.
But Syd happens to know,
the hole in the fence
isn't about fugees getting out.
- It's about Fishies getting in.
- Go away.
Syd also happens to know that the Army's
gonna blow the shit out of this place.
But don't worry.
Syd is here to get you out.
Fuck off. Go away.
Go on. Piss off!
Get your fucking dog.
What you got there?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
- No?
Like to show me?
I don't have anything.
- It's nothing.
- If it's nothing, then I can have a look.
- Let me see.
- No.
It's okay. Let me see.
Jesus Christ.
- That's a...
- That's right.
We got a baby.
And now we need a rowboat.
Can you help us?
Get her up. Get her up. We need to go.
Can you help us get a boat?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just get her up.
We need to go. We need to go now.
- What's she saying?
- Fuck knows.
Bad! Bad! Bad!
She doesn't want us to go.
Shut up.
We need to go.
Syd was watching television
last night with Mummy.
She's a sweet old soul.
Dying of cancer. It's heartbreaking.
And then the news came on,
and you two were on it.
Something about a cop killer.
Something about a big reward.
Syd then finds out
the Fishes are looking for you.
So Syd thinks,
"If the Fishes are looking for you,
"and the coppers
are looking for you,
"you people are
first class commodities."
Shut the fuck up! Shut up!
Down, down, down!
Now, Syd has a baby.
Bad! Bad! Bad!
Marichka!
I'll fucking kill you,
you bitch! I'll fucking kill you!
Bitch. You bitch.
Baby! Marichka baby!
Quick, quick. The baby!
My baby! She took...
I'll fucking kill you,
you gypsy bitch!
I'm gonna blow
your fucking brains out.
Go, go!
Fuck! Shit.
How are you doing?
- How are you?
- It hurts.
Marichka, we need a boat.
A boat. The sea, a boat, a rowboat.
We need a boat.
A fucking boat! A boat.
- A rowboat!
- Yes.
Hurry.
- You okay? Come on.
- Hurry.
Hurry. Hurry.
It's okay.
Look at that, Theo.
They love my baby.
I want to call her Bazouka.
"Bazouka"?
You don't like it?
I was getting used to "Froley".
Froley's a man's name.
What is he thinking,
giving you a boy's name? You're a girl.
We have a boat. Stay here.
In one hour, we go.
Thanks.
Human Project real?
It better be.
Drop your gun! Drop your gun!
Put your hands up!
Put your fucking hands in the air!
Okay, is clear! Is clear!
Hands above your head
and fucking move that here.
You killed my fucking cousin!
Get on your knees!
On your knees, you fucking...
He was 19!
Don't kill him!
Watch the flanks!
Kee. Thank God.
You'll be safe now.
How's the child?
You put their lives at risk.
Just let her go.
You don't know what you're doing.
No? Look around you.
It's the Uprising.
And they haven't even
seen the baby. Let's go.
No! Get off...
Not in front of the girl.
Wait till we get around the corner.
Then do them all.
Come on!
Oh, lads
You should have
seen us gannin'
Passing the folks along the road
And all of them was starin'
And all the lads and lasses there
They all had smilin' faces
Fuck!
Sorry. Sorry.
Move it! Get her inside!
Faron!
Get her inside!
Get her in the building now!
Now! Move it! Now!
Sarge, left flank!
Flank the fuckers!
Don't shoot! Citizens! We citizens!
Go check the roof!
I was carrying
the baby up the stairs.
I started crying.
I'd forgotten what they looked like.
They're so beautiful.
They're so tiny.
Julian was wrong!
She thought it could be peaceful!
But how can it be peaceful
when they try to take away your dignity?
We need him, Theo!
We need the baby. We need him!
It's a girl, Luke.
A girl?
I had a sister.
Theo! Theo!
You okay?
How is she?
Annoyed.
My God, the baby.
Move back! Fucking move back!
Stop! Cease fire! Cease firing!
Cease firing!
We've got two coming through,
coming out.
Second floor, left!
Medic!
Marichka!
No, Marichka no go. You go.
- You go.
- Marichka, come. Marichka.
- Marichka, get in the boat!
- Go, boat!
The buoy! Theo, the buoy!
You okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
What a day.
We're too late, aren't we?
No. No, we're fine.
But they said they wouldn't wait.
Trust me. They'll come back.
I'm bleeding. Jesus, shit, I'm bleeding!
- No, no, no, it's me.
- I'm bleeding everywhere.
It's me.
What?
He got me.
Bad?
No. I'm fine.
Keep her close, Kee.
Whatever happens,
whatever they say,
you keep her close.
It's going to be okay.
She's probably got wind. Wind her.
Put her on your shoulder.
Just... Just tap her back.
Gently.
There you go.
Oh, Jesus.
Dylan.
I'll call my baby "Dylan".
It's a girl's name, too.
Theo?
Theo!
Theo, the boat.
The boat!
It's okay.
We are safe now.
We're safe.